CV Dawid Kuzbiel

IT Support/Operations technician



**** 0734-08 08 08

Dawid.Kuzbiel@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/dawidkuzbiel

www.github.com/madebydawid

www.madebydawid.github.io



I am an IT Support/Operations technician with expertise in Microsoft 365 and Azure, as well as experience in technical troubleshooting, network configuration, and system administration. Solution-oriented with strong analytical skills and a great team player. Certified and updated on the latest industry trends with an ambition to continue developing in IT and becoming a leading specialist focusing on DevOps, Cloud and Security solutions.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2024-09 - Present

IT Technician / Wise IT, Gothenburg

- Provided user support onsite and through various tools, resolving issues related to OS, networks, and M365.
- Managed AD administration and user access.
- Configured and maintained access control, alarm systems, and charging stations.
- Onboarded/Offboarded users with setup and configuration of computers, accounts, and iPhones.
- Improved tagging systems in the ticketing system and developed onboarding documentation.

IT Tools: Active Directory, Azure Portal, Office 365, Microsoft 365

2019 - 2024

Behavioral Scientist / Aranäsgymnasiet, Kungsbacka

- Contributed to improved well-being (+7%) and attendance (+12%) through systematic quality work (SKA), as reported in 2020.
- Conducted health-promoting initiatives through lectures, workshops, and guidelines; delivered approximately 25 sessions to nearly 1,000 students.
- Performed technical troubleshooting, resolving issues with projectors, TV screens, and screen sharing, ensuring software compatibility for students both in and outside the classroom.
- Provided technical support during the COVID-19 pandemic, assisting students and teachers with Teams connections.
- OneDrive management, file handling, folder structures, printing, recordings, and more.

IT Tools: Microsoft 365, Windows 10, MacOS, Office 365

2018 - 2019

Project Manager / Roofia AB, Kungsbacka

- Led a team of three, successfully installing solar panels on multiple properties.
- Played a key role in the startup and development, planning and coordinating solar panel solutions.
- Managed customer and supplier communications via email, phone, and onsite visits.
- Created drawings and cost estimates.

IT Tools: PvSolar, Outlook, Windows

2018

Counselor / Cityläkarna, Borås

- Conducted assessments and therapy sessions for patients with various mental health conditions.
- Handled documentation and confidentiality requirements as part of the role.

IT Tools: Windows, Documentation software

2007 - 2017

Welder / Various Companies

EDUCATION & COURSES

April 2024 – August 2024

IT-Support / Operation Technician / Lexicon IT Proffs, Stockholm

- MS-900: Microsoft 365 Fundamentals Cloud Fundamentals of Microsoft 365.
- SC-900: Microsoft 365 Security Fundamentals Security basics for Microsoft 365 & Azure.
- MS-500: Microsoft 365 Security Administrator Advanced security for Microsoft 365 & Azure.
- MD-102: Endpoint Administrator Windows operating system installation and administration.
- MS-700 Teams Administrator Deployment, administration and troubleshooting in a corporate environment.
- Cisco Networking Basic Fundamentals course in Cisco-networking and computer communications.
- Virtualization & Hyper-V Virtualization focused lab environment.
- AZ-800 Server 2022 Server management in hybrid environments on-premises & Azure
- AZ-900 Azure Fundamentals Covers Azure broadly, with an overview of functionalities and services.
- Information Security Data integrity and confidentiality
- PowerShell In several course modules listed above
- ITIL 4

2015 - 2018

Bachelor Cognitive Neuroscience / University of Skövde, Sweden

Bachelor of Science in Cognitive Neuroscience, emphasizing analytical thinking, problem-solving, and understanding of human behavior and cognition. Proficient in data analysis, research methodologies, and critical thinking, with a strong foundation in scientific inquiry and interdisciplinary approaches. Seeking to leverage cognitive science insights to contribute effectively to IT projects and solutions.

SKILLS

Technical Skills • Microsoft 365 Administration • Server Administration (*Windows, Linux*) • Active Directory • Operating Systems (*Windows, Linux, MacOS*) • Networking • Scripting (*Bash, PowerShell*) • Virtualization (*VM-Ware, Hyper-V, Oracle VM VirtualBox*) • Cloud Platforms (*Azure*) • Version Control (*Git, GitHub*) • Troubleshooting • HTML • CSS • VSCode

Soft Skills • Effective Communicator • Resourceful • Support-oriented • Fast Learner • Adaptable • High Social Skills

CERTIFICATIONS

- SC-900: Security, Compliance & Identity fundamentals (Certification)
- MS-900: 365 Fundamentals Cloud (Certification)
- Cisco Networking Basics (Certification)
- Cisco Operating Systems Basics (<u>Certification</u>)
- AZ-900: Azure Fundamentals (*Currently Pursuing*)



ADDITIONAL PROJECTS & EXPERIENCE

2024

GitHub Pages Website – Project available on my GitHub

- Developed a personal website using the Jekyll theme Chirpy to showcase personal projects and information.
- Customized code in VS Code and managed version control with Git via Bash CLI.
- Implemented a CI/CD pipeline using GitHub Actions for seamless deployment.

IT Tools: Azure Monitor, Azure VM, Dashboard, Automation, Bash, CLI

2024

Docker Projects – Project available on my GitHub

• Created a Hello World Docker app with a Nginx web server in a container.

IT Tools: *Docker, Nginx*

2024

Azure Monitoring Projects – Project available on my GitHub

- Monitored CPU and RAM on Azure VMs with automated alerts and autoscaling.
- Created a real-time dashboard for monitoring multiple resources.

IT Tools: Azure Monitor, Azure VM, Dashboard, Automation, Bash, CLI

2024

Virtual Lab Environment – Project available on my GitHub

- I created a virtual lab environment using Oracle VM.
- Installed Windows Server 2019 with a Domain Controller, configured DHCP, DNS, and Active Directory.
- Simulated an organization by adding over 1000 users to AD using a PowerShell script.

IT Tools: Oracle VM, Windows Server 2019, Windows 10 Pro, DHCP, DNS, DC, AD, PowerShell

2023

DNS Spam & Ad Blocker – Project available on my GitHub

- Installed and configured an ad blocker service on my Raspberry Pi to filter unwanted ads on my home network and all connected devices.
- Set Raspberry Pi as the default DHCP server for IPv4 distribution to my home network.

IT Tools: Linux, IPv4, DNS, SSH

I like to challenge myself with the exposure of different IT technologies • Canoeing & Camping • Martial Arts • Golf • Philosophy

LANGUAGES

English – Excellent verbal and written communication skills.

Swedish – Excellent verbal and written communication skills.

Polish – Native language.

REFERENCES

Good references available upon request.